ALİ YILMAZ

Software Developer

CONTACT

+905380459938 aliyilmaz9977@gmail.com aliyilmaz.site

EDUCATION

AYYİLDİZ ANADOLU

High School

2014-2018

YALOVA UNIVERSITY

Computer Science

2018-2024

SKILLS

Flutter Development
Web Development
Backend Development
Game Development
Team Leading

VOLUNTEERING

Yalova University Artificial Intelligence Society Team Lead

Yalova Google Developer Groups Team Lead and Organizer

SUMMARY

I have II years of experience as a computer engineer. I am proficient in a wide range of technologies and programming languages, including Flutter, Unity, JavaScript, Express, Vue, Node.js, C, C++, Go, Php, MongoDB, Sql. I have previously worked on various projects in full-time and part-time roles, achieving successes. With my analytical thinking skills and ability to come up with creative solutions to complex technical problems, I have made valuable contributions to projects. I am also team-oriented and possess strong communication skills. I am focused on continuous self-improvement through my fast learning ability and interest in staying updated with the latest technologies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE TEAM LEAD & FLUTTER DEVELOPER

Vessac Game Studios

2022 - Present

- · Flutter app design and development
- Unity game development and team management
- Finished 4 Unity games
- Finished 3 Flutter applications

FLUTTER DEVELOPER

Sezer Ai Technology

2023-Present

- Flutter app design and development
- Firebase design.
- Flutter app ui design.

TESTER

Freelance

2023-Present

- Website manuel testing.
- Web vulnerabilities testing.
- Website user testing.
- Website session testing.
- Website api testing.